Guide to the Doris Duke Foundation records, 1934-2009 (bulk 1948-1982)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1934-2009
  - New Jersey: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains Somerville Free Public Library, Hillsborough Boys Football Association, Somerville Area Girl Scout Council, Hillsborough Township Volunteer Fire Company No. 2,Somerville Fire Department, Rolling Hills Girl Scout Council, Somerset County Day Care Association, Somerset County Tuberculosis and Health Association, Somerset Valley Community Chest, N.J. State Museum, Somerville-Raritan Area United Campaign, and Somerset Valley Y.M.C.A, 1937–1974 (4 of 4) (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Historical Society: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1962 tax exemption, 1967–1971 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - New York Association for the Blind (Lighthouse) – The Ophthalmological Foundation: Donation, Current Files, 1951–1969 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - New York Botanical Garden: Donations, Current Files, 1952–1961, 1975–1978 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - New York City Mission Society and New York Protestant Episcopal Mission Society: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1971 tax exemption, 1952–1973 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - New York Public Library: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1947 and 1970 tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1977 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - New York State Citizens Committee for the Public Schools: Donations, Current Files, 1955–1961 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - New York Zoological Society: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1939 tax exemption, 1947–1955, 1961–1979 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Newport: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and tax exemptions. Contains Newport Police Relief Association, Newport Permanent Firemen’s Pension Association, Newport Mansion and Museum Corporation, Newport Cliff Walk Commission, and Preservation Association of Newport County, 1957–1961, 1964–1966, 1970–1974 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1969 and 1971 tax exemptions, legal filings between May E. McFarland and Doris Duke, and administrative information regarding NRF, 1968–1974 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Newton Foundation – Psychiatric Research Institute of Beverly Hills: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1968 and 1969 tax exemptions and Articles of Incorporation, 1966–1969, 1973–1974 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Nightingale Bamford School – Tucker Children: Donations, Current Files, 1962–1975 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - O – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Contains L’orphelinat Saint-Marcel (Action Catholique Francaise) and Overseas Press Club of America, 1953–1955, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Oceanic Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and 1965, 1970, and 1971 tax exemptions, 1971–1974 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Orentreich Foundation for the Advancement of Science: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1964 tax exemption, 1967–1975 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Osborne Association: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1935, 1938, and 1971 tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1975 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - P – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions. Contains Phoenix House, Pine Mountain Settlement House (affiliated with Berea College), Presbyterian Church – Kwangju Hospital (Korea), Puerto Rican Social Services, Peninsula Volunteers, and Dr. Myron Prinzmetal, 1953–1972 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Pantages, Lloyd A. (Board Member): Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1954–1973 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - People to People Health Foundation – Project Hope: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1959 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1960–1975 (1 of 2) (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - People to People Health Foundation – Project Hope: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1959 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1960–1975 (2 of 2) (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Play Schools Association – Mrs. Adele Rosenwald Levy (Mrs. David): Donations, Current Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1943–1974 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Police Athletic League: Donations, Current Files, 1952–1962, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Professional Children’s School: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1934 and 1948 tax exemptions, 1954–1968 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - R – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings. Contains Rehearsal Club, Luis Rivera, Rosenberg Foundation, Rhode Island Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, and Madeline Dane Ross, 1954–1972 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Recording for the Blind: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1952 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1954–1972 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Research to Prevent Blindness: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and 1961 and 1972 tax exemptions, 1962–1973 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Rosebud Sioux Indians, South Dakota – Gift of Cattle: Donations, Current Files. Includes chattel Mortgage and correspondence with Duke Farms. See also, National Congress of American Indians (A.R.R.O.W.), 1958–1965, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - S – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions and correspondence of Independent Aid, Inc. Contains Saint Anthony’s Church of Portsmouth, R.I., St. Anne’s Foundation, St. Marcel Orphanage, Paris (National Council of Catholic Women), Symphony of Musical Arts, Scudder Memorial Hospital, Speech and Hearing Institute, and Siena, Italy (Orphanage), 1949–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - S – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping, tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains St. Marks Church In-The-Bouwerie, Sculptors’ Guild, Senior Personnel Employment Committee, Wake County Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, Society for the Rehabilitation of the Facially Disfigured, Southern Pediatric Seminar, and Stadium Concerts, 1949–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Saint George’s School – Newport, R.I.: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1971 tax exemption, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Salvation Army: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1955 and 1972 tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947–1974 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Somerset County Park Commission – Somerville, N.J.: Donations, Current Files, 1964, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Somerset Hospital – Somerville, N.J.: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1953–1967, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - State Communities Aid Association: Donations, Current Files. Includes photograph, 1935 and 1970 tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1934–1975 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Studio Watts Workshop: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1966 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1968–1973 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Supreme Court, Matrimonial Division – Association of the Bar of the City of New York: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1955–1957 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - T – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions. Contains Temple University and John Tracy Clinic, 1952, 1958, 1967–1972 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Tolstoy Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1972 tax exemption, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1972 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Trail Blazers Camps: Donations, Current Files. Includes Lease Agreement between Trail Blazers Camps and Doris Duke and 1937 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1954–1974, 1979 (1 of 2) (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Trail Blazers Camps: Donations, Current Files. Includes Lease Agreement between Trail Blazers Camps and Doris Duke and 1937 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1954–1974, 1979 (2 of 2) (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Travelers Aid Society of New York: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1944 and 1971 tax exemptions, 1952–1977 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Tri-County Children’s Center: Donations, Current Files. Includes photograph and 1958 tax exemption, 1959–1965 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - U – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains United Nations Refugee Fund, U.S. Committee of the International Conference of Social Work, Union Theological Seminary, United Cerebral Palsy of New York City, United Jewish Appeal, United Nations International School, and United Neighborhood Houses, 1948–1966 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Union Settlement: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, 1938 and 1970 tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1952–1975 (1 of 2) (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Union Settlement: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, 1938 and 1970 tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1952–1975 (2 of 2) (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Unitarian Service Committee: Donations, Current Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Some letters in French, 1950–1963 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - United Family and Children’s Society: Donations, Current Files, 1956–1957, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - United Hospital: Donations, Current Files, 1942, 1952–1965 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - University of Southern California – Dental Ambassador Program: Includes clippings, photographs, and 1934 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1969–1973 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Urban League of Greater New York and National Urban League: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1968 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - V – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains Venereal Disease Program (H.E.W.), Veterans Hospital Radio Guild, and Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1950–1958 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Assistance League: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1966 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1959, 1966–1974 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Visiting Nurse Service of New York: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1944 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1950–1976 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Vocational Advisory Service: Donations, Current Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1970 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Vocational Foundation: Donations, Current Files, 1957–1960 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Volunteer Service Photographers: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1947 tax exemption, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1963 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - W – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and tax exemptions. Contains Watumull Foundation, Washington City Orphan Asylum (Hillcrest Children’s Center), Washington Square Association, White House Conference on Children and Youth, Michael Wilkoss (Catholic Relief Services), Jack E. Whitehouse, Mary Lou Williams, Garland Wilson, and World Wildlife Fund, 1953–1969 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Western College for Women: Donations, Current Files. Includes photographs, 1955–1963, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Wiltwyck School for Boys: Donations, Current Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1944–1965 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Windham Children’s Service: Donations, Current Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1962, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Women’s Prison Association of New York: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1971 tax exemption and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1974 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Donations, Current Files, 1961–1968 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - World Federation for Mental Health: Donations, Current Files, 1953–1968 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - World Rehabilitation Fund: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and 1962 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1956–1975 (1 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - World Rehabilitation Fund: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and 1962 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1956–1975 (2 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - World University Service: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and photographs, 1952–1964 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Y – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1965 tax exemption. Contains Young Audiences (New York Committee) and Y.W.C.A. World Service Building Program, 1960, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Yale-In-China Association: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photograph, and 1939 tax exemptions, 1966–1975 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Donations, Current Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1951–1958 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Y.W.C.A.: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and 1944 and 1971 tax exemptions, 1952–1975 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Y.W.C.A. – National Board and Delhi School of Social Work: Donations, Current Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1960, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - A: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes photographs and tax exemptions. Contains Alice Lloyd College, American Veterans Committee, and various other organizations, 1974-1975 (1 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - A: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains American Cancer Society – New Jersey Division, American Farm School, and various other organizations, 1974–1975 (2 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - A: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains American Cancer Society – New Jersey and New York City Divisions, African Students Service Association, and various other organizations, 1974–1975 (3 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - B: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes correspondence with W.C. Davison (Board Member and Duke University School of Medicine Dean), 1957–1973 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - B: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clippings and tax exemptions. Contains Bank Street College of Education, Beekman Downtown Hospital, Boy Scouts of America, and various other organizations, 1974–1976 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - C: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains Community Council of Greater New York and various other organizations, 1974–1976 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - D: Donations, 1975 Denials, 1957–1960, 1969–1970 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - D: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains Duke University School of Engineering and various other organizations, 1974–1975 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - E: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains East Harlem Interfaith, Emergency Land Fund, and various other organizations, 1973–1975 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - F: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes correspondence with W.C. Davison (Board Member and Duke University School of Medicine Dean), 1959, 1965, 1969–1975 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - G: Donations, 1975 Denials, 1974–1975 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - H: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains Harlem School of the Arts, Hillsborough Youth Council, and various other organizations, 1960–1961, 1973–1975 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - I: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains United States Department of the Interior – Bureau of Indian Affairs and various other organizations, 1974–1975 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - J: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes photograph. Contains Jobs For Youth, Jubilee Singers, and various other organizations, 1957–1960, 1966, 1973–1975 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - K: Donations, 1975 Denials, 1952–1953, 1956, 1960–1961 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - K: Donations, 1975 Denials, 1966–1967, 1973–1975 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - L: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains Lawyers’ Committee for Civil Rights Under Law and various other organizations, 1962–1965, 1974–1975 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Mc: Donations, 1975 Denials, 1957–1962, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - M: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes photographs. Contains Maimonides Medical Center, National Committee for Security and Justice in the Middle East, and various other organizations, 1951–1962, 1966–1967, 1971–1972 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - M: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clippings, 1974–1975 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - N: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clipping and tax exemptions. Contains various New York, New Jersey, Newport, and Native American organizations, 1962–1963, 1971–1975 (1 of 3) (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - N: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clipping and tax exemptions. Contains various New York, New Jersey, Newport, and Native American organizations, 1962–1963, 1971–1975 (2 of 3) (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - N: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clipping and tax exemptions. Contains various New York, New Jersey, Newport, and Native American organizations, 1962–1963, 1971–1975 (3 of 3) (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - O: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes photographs, 1966, 1974–1975 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - P: Donations, 1975 Denials. Contains Planned Parenthood and various other organizations, 1957–1960, 1966, 1974–1975 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Q: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clippings, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - R: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clippings, 1961–1964, 1969, 1973–1975 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - S: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clippings, photographs, and correspondence with W.C. Davison (Board Member and Duke University School of Medicine Dean), 1954–1957, 1960–1965 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - S: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clippings and tax exemptions. Contains Save the Bay (Rhode Island), 1974–1975 (1 of 3) (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - S: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clippings and tax exemptions. Contains Save the Bay (Rhode Island), 1974–1975 (2 of 3) (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - S: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clippings and tax exemptions. Contains Save the Bay (Rhode Island), 1974–1975 (3 of 3) (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - T: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes correspondence with W.C. Davison (Board Member and Duke University School of Medicine Dean). Contains Trail Blazers Camps, Edger Tufts Memorial Association (Banner Elk, N.C.), and various other organizations, 1955–1963, 1973–1975 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - U: Donations, 1975 Denials, 1974–1975 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - V: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes tax exemptions, 1974–1976 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - W: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clipping and tax exemptions, 1974–1975 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Y–Z: Donations, 1975 Denials. Includes clipping. Contains various chapters of Y.M.C.A. and Y.W.C.A., 1973–1975 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - A: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes clipping and tax exemption, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - B: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - B: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - C: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes photograph. Contains Citizens Committee for New York City, 1976 (1 of 3) (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - C: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes photograph. Contains Citizens Committee for New York City, 1976 (2 of 3) (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - C: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes photograph. Contains Citizens Committee for New York City, 1976 (3 of 3) (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - D: Donations, 1976 Denials. Contains Deborah Heart and Lung Center, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - E: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes tax exemption. Contains Echo, Inc. (Elderly—Communication—Help—Outreach, Trenton, N.J.) and Essex Education Institute (Nutley, N.J.), 1976 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - F: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes tax exemptions and clipping. Contains City of New York Fire Department, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - G: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1975–1976 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - H: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes tax exemptions and architectural drawings. Contains Hofstra University, 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - H: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes tax exemptions and architectural drawings. Contains Hofstra University, 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - I: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - J: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes tax exemption, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - K: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - L: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes tax exemption, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - M: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes tax exemption, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - N: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes clippings and tax exemption. Contains National Burn Victim Foundation (West Orange, N.J.), 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - N: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes clippings and tax exemption. Contains National Burn Victim Foundation (West Orange, N.J.), 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - O: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - P: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Q: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes clippings, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - R: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - S: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes clippings and tax exemption. Contains Saint Joseph’s Convent (Woodbridge, N.J.) and Somerset Neighborhood Health Clinic, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - T: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes clippings, tax exemptions, and engineering drawing. Contains Trail Blazers Camps, Trinity Square Repertory Company, and Plan for the Improvement of Bonnie Brae Farm (Bernards, N.J.), 1976 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - U: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes tax exemption, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - V: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - W: Donations, 1976 Denials, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - X–Z: Donations, 1976 Denials. Includes clipping, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - A: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - B: Donations, 1977 Denials. Includes tax exemptions, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - C: Donations, 1977 Denials. Includes clippings, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - D: Donations, 1977 Denials. Includes clipping. Contains Deborah Hospital (Somerville, N.J.), 1977 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - F: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - G: Donations, 1977 Denials. Includes clipping, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - H: Donations, 1977 Denials. Includes clippings, 1976–1977 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - I: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1976–1977 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - J: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - K: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - L: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - M: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1976–1977 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - N: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - O: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - P: Donations, 1977 Denials. Contains Printmaking Council of New Jersey, 1976–1977 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - R: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - S: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1975–1977 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - U: Donations, 1977 Denials, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - V: Donations, 1977 Denials. Includes clipping, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - W: Donations, 1977 Denials. Includes clippings, 1976–1977 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - X–Z: Donations, 1977 Denials. Includes clippings, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Self-Realization Fellowship Church: Miscellaneous Donation Files. Includes 1936 and 1950 tax exemptions, 1956–1957, 1963–1977 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - American Indian Oral History Project (University of Utah and University of South Dakota): Miscellaneous Donation Files. Includes numerous reports, 1969–1972 (1 of 3) (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - American Indian Oral History Project (University of Utah and University of South Dakota): Miscellaneous Donation Files. Includes numerous reports, 1969–1972 (2 of 3) (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - American Indian Oral History Project (University of Utah and University of South Dakota): Miscellaneous Donation Files. Includes numerous reports, 1969–1972 (3 of 3) (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Optometric Center of New York – Alden N. Haffner: Miscellaneous Donation Files. Includes 1957 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1970–1974 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Orentreich Foundation for the Advancement of Science: Miscellaneous Donation Files. Includes 1971 and 1972 tax exemptions, 1971-1972, 1978-1979 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Martha Graham Center of Contemporary Dance: Miscellaneous Donation Files, 1975–1978 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Brearley School: Miscellaneous Donation Files, 1976–1977 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Denied Donation Requests: Miscellaneous Donation Files, 1976–1977 (1 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 9)